- id: ckw-l14-3089
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - トラック
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l14-3095
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - テキスト
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l14-3106
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - バイク
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l14-3111
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - レンズ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l14-3119
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ハウス
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l14-3128
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ラーメン
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l14-3156
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - プロセス
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l14-3184
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - キス
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l14-3186
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - コート
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l14-3201
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - リーグ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l14-3218
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ニュー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l14-3220
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ニーズ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l14-3223
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ミス
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l14-3225
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - サラダ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l14-3242
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - オフ
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []
